{
    "id": "43_Education_10",
    "claim": "Mexico. - The rector of UNAM, Enrique Luis Graue, quoted the media to a press conference to inform that from next year the time of graduation of the degrees of Philosophy and Sociology of the Universities of the whole country will be limited to a maximum of'years '(only one more than normally lasts the degree) in order to stop the formation of 'fossils 'and thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure. Enrique points out that they decided to implement the strategy in these careers as it is where the largest number of 'fossils 'are registered, that is, students who retest on purpose, take only one or two per year, or leave school to return to the next semester in order to prolong their stay at the University since it becomes their comfort zone:You may be interested Lolita de la Vega wins demand to prevent TV Azteca from retracting Sailor Moon 'Bachelors of Philosophy and Sociology are designed to end up in a maximum  years, in these races it is where a greater number of guerrilla chairos are registered but also where there is the largest number of fossils. For these people their institution becomes their comfort zone and they do their best to prolong their stay because they feel a terrible fear of going out into the real world. At the university they feel part of something, they are afraid that when they graduate they will become ghosts and no one will take them into account. Every student in a public university costs the state more than USD 1,000 pesos a semester, it is not fair for the government to pay that amount for someone who only enrolls to take one or two subjects each  months to extend their stay, which often becomes up to  years ', he said. Luis mentioned that these degrees last  semesters, and from next year they will only be given the opportunity to study at the institution other  semesters more in case they are delayed: 'there are people who literally last  semesters at the University, this is going to end. The students of these careers will not be able to give low subjects, and if they reprove on purpose we will pass them even if they do not want to. If the student still refuses to go out and misses his year of tolerance then he will be automatically discharged and will not be able to re-enter the university anymore, neither his career nor any other. It's not fair that his whim causes the government to spend a millionaire censer that can be invested in infrastructure or new material. From  they will have a year of tolerance to graduate, it is the only way we can end fossils ', he said. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.elruinaversal.com",
    "date": "19/05/2017",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "Mexico .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elruinaversal.com report that Mexico was a country?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the location of Mexico in 2017?",
                    "score": 0.723,
                    "answers": "that|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Mexico and the United States?",
                    "score": 0.6733,
                    "answers": "that Mexico|npadvmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- The rector of UNAM, Enrique Luis Graue , quoted the media to a press conference to inform that from next year the time of graduation of the degrees of Philosophy and Sociology of the Universities of Mexico will be limited to a maximum of'years '(only one more than normally lasts the degree) in order to stop the formation of 'fossils 'and thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the rector of UNAM?",
                    "answer": "Enrique Luis Graue"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Luis Graue say about the creation of fossils?",
                    "score": 0.7583,
                    "answers": "in order to stop the formation of ' fossils ' and thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure|prep\torder to stop the formation of ' fossils ' and thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure|pobj\tto stop the formation of ' fossils ' and thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the rector of UNAM say about graduation of the degrees of Philosophy and Sociology of the Universities of Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.7496,
                    "answers": "that - The rector of UNAM , Enrique Luis Graue , quoted the media to a press conference to inform that from next year the time of graduation of the degrees of Philosophy and Sociology of the Universities of Mexico will be limited to a maximum of'years ' ( only one more than normally lasts the degree ) in order to stop the formation of ' fossils ' and thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of creating fossils?",
                    "score": 0.6613,
                    "answers": "the formation of ' fossils '|dobj\tfossils|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the budget of universities in Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6496,
                    "answers": "thus prevent universities from having unnecessary expenditure|conj\tfrom having unnecessary expenditure|prep\thaving unnecessary expenditure|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the graduation rate of students in the University of Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6463,
                    "answers": "of Philosophy and Sociology of the Universities of Mexico|prep\tPhilosophy and Sociology of the Universities of Mexico|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The rector of UNAM, Enrique Luis Graue points out that they decided to implement the strategy in these careers as it is where the largest number of 'fossils 'are registered, that is, students who retest on purpose, take only one or two per year, or leave school to return to the next semester in order to prolong stay at the University since the University becomes comfort zone:You may be interested Lolita de la Vega wins demand to prevent TV Azteca from retracting Sailor Moon 'Bachelors of Philosophy and Sociology are designed to end up in a maximum  years, in Bachelors of Philosophy and Sociology it is where a greater number of guerrilla chairos are registered but also where there is the largest number of fossils.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who wins demand to prevent TV Azteca from retracting Sailor Moon?",
                    "answer": "Lolita de la Vega"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many guber chairos are registered each year at UNAM?",
                    "score": 0.7028,
                    "answers": "Sailor Moon ' Bachelors of Philosophy and Sociology|nsubjpass\ta greater number of guerrilla chairos|nsubjpass\tof guerrilla chairos|prep\tguerrilla chairos|pobj\twhere a greater number of guerrilla chairos are registered but also where there is the largest number of fossils|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the proposal of the rector of UNAM?",
                    "score": 0.6532,
                    "answers": "demand to prevent TV Azteca from retracting Sailor Moon ' Bachelors of Philosophy and Sociology are designed to end up in a maximum|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For these people institution becomes comfort zone and these people do best to prolong stay because these people feel a terrible fear of going out into the real world.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elruinaversal report that institution becomes comfort zone?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why do people fear going out into the real world?",
                    "score": 0.8101,
                    "answers": "these people do best to prolong stay because these people feel a terrible fear of going out into the real world|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "At the university these people feel part of something, these people are afraid that when these people graduate these people will become ghosts and no one will take these people into account.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are people afraid of when they graduate from a university?",
                    "answer": "when these people graduate these people will become ghosts"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people graduate from the University of Iowa?",
                    "score": 0.7567,
                    "answers": "no one will take these people into account|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the number of ghost people at the University of Kansas?",
                    "score": 0.6281,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tthese|det\t,|punct\tthese|det\tthat|mark\twhen|advmod\tthese|det\tthese|det\twill|aux\tand|cc\twill|aux\tthese|det\taccount|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Every student in a public university costs the state more than USD 1,000 pesos a semester, it is not fair for the government to pay that amount for someone who only enrolls to take one or two subjects each  months to extend their stay, which often becomes up to  years ', he said.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much does it cost the government to pay students to extend their stay?",
                    "score": 0.836,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj\tmore than USD 1,000 pesos a semester each   months to extend their stay , which often becomes up to|dobj\tit|nsubj\tfair|acomp\tfor|mark\ttwo|conj\twhich|nsubj\twhich often becomes up to|relcl\tup|quantmod\tup to|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the cost of a student's stay in a public university?",
                    "score": 0.7902,
                    "answers": "one or two|nummod\ttheir|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the amount that the government pays for students who enrolls to take one or two subjects?",
                    "score": 0.7462,
                    "answers": "for the government to pay that amount for someone who only enrolls to take one or two subjects|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Luis mentioned that these degrees last  semesters, and from next year they will only be given the opportunity to study at the institution other  semesters more in case they are delayed: 'there are people who literally last  semesters at the University, this is going to end.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.elruinaversal.com report that Luis mentioned that these degrees last semesters?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Luis say about student deferments?",
                    "score": 0.759,
                    "answers": "will|aux\tthe institution|pobj\tother|amod\t:|punct\t'|punct\tthe University|pobj\tto end|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the average graduation rate of students who graduate from a university?",
                    "score": 0.7324,
                    "answers": "these degrees|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The students of these careers will not be able to give low subjects, and if they reprove on purpose we will pass them even if they do not want to.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elruinaversal.com report that students of these careers will not be able to give low subjects?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to give low subjects?",
                    "score": 0.8315,
                    "answers": "to give low subjects|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many students do not want to pass their course credits?",
                    "score": 0.7906,
                    "answers": "of these careers|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the requirements for completing a course?",
                    "score": 0.7297,
                    "answers": "low subjects|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of reprove on purpose?",
                    "score": 0.6547,
                    "answers": "if they reprove on purpose we will pass them even if they do not want to|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If the student still refuses to go out and misses his year of tolerance then he will be automatically discharged and will not be able to re-enter the university anymore, neither his career nor any other.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happens to a student if he misses his year of tolerance?",
                    "answer": "he will be automatically discharged"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to be discharged from a university?",
                    "score": 0.7039,
                    "answers": "that If the student still refuses to go out and misses his year of tolerance then he will be automatically discharged and will not be able to re - enter the university anymore , neither his career nor any other|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What would happen if a student refused to go out and miss his year of tolerance?",
                    "score": 0.6789,
                    "answers": "If the student still refuses to go out and misses his year of tolerance|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of a student being discharged from college?",
                    "score": 0.6406,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the punishment for not going out and missing a year of tolerance?",
                    "score": 0.5953,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that If the student still refuses to go out and misses his year of tolerance then he will be automatically discharged and will not be able to re - enter the university anymore , neither his career nor any other|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of tolerance?",
                    "score": 0.5673,
                    "answers": "of tolerance|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's not fair that his whim causes the government to spend a millionaire censer that can be invested in infrastructure or new material.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of censer did Elruinaversal say the government should not spend?",
                    "answer": "millionaire"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much money did the government spend on infrastructure or new material?",
                    "score": 0.8571,
                    "answers": "that It 's not fair that his whim causes the government to spend a millionaire censer that can be invested in infrastructure or new material|ccomp\tthat his whim causes the government to spend a millionaire censer that can be invested in infrastructure or new material|ccomp\tthe government to spend a millionaire censer that can be invested in infrastructure or new material|ccomp\tmillionaire|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of a censer?",
                    "score": 0.7652,
                    "answers": "his whim|nsubj\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the amount spent on the censer?",
                    "score": 0.721,
                    "answers": "or|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "From  they will have a year of tolerance to graduate, it is the only way we can end fossils ', he said.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Elruinaversal say they would have a year of tolerance to graduate?",
                    "answer": "it is the only way we can end fossils"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can we end fossils?",
                    "score": 0.8235,
                    "answers": "can|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many years of tolerance does it take for fossils to graduate?",
                    "score": 0.8071,
                    "answers": "a year of tolerance|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the benefits of tolerance to graduate fossils?",
                    "score": 0.7888,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tto|aux\t,|punct\tthe|det\t'|punct\t,|punct\the|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are fossils?",
                    "score": 0.7522,
                    "answers": "fossils|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best way to end fossils?",
                    "score": 0.7466,
                    "answers": " |dep\tthey|nsubj\tthey will have a year of tolerance to graduate|ccomp\ta|det\tto graduate|advcl\tthey will have a year of tolerance to graduate , it is the only way we can end fossils|pcomp\tonly|amod\twww.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that From   they will have a year of tolerance to graduate , it is the only way we can end fossils ' , he said|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}